A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Council on the Environment, 1970-1988
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 29657], 1970-1977., Extent: 14.3 cu. ft. (39 boxes). (Box 1-39)
  - General Assembly worksheets, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - General legislation, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly reports, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Legislative procedure, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - House of Delegates correspondence, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Senate correspondence, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Conflict of Interest Provision in DEP bill, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bills passed, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bills carried over, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bills P.B.I., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - State Air Pollution Control Board (Edgar B. Boynton), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries (Dr. Allan A. Hoffman), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Virginia's Bicentennial Spruce-Up Campaign, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee on Offshore Ports and Exploration of the Commission to Study Energy Crisis, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management (First), Original Report, 1975 October (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management (First), Correspondence, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management (First), Speeches, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management (First), Questionnaires, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management (First), Participants and proceedings, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management (First), Packet and brochures, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management (First), Working papers, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Air Transportation System Study, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Governor's Management Study, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Critical Environmental Areas Study, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Land Use Task Force, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Land Use Task Force, 1971-1973 (Box 8a, Folder 1-5)
  - Space technology, 1975-1976 (Box 8a, Folder 6)
  - NASEPA (National Association of State Environmental Protection Agencies), Agencies, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - NASEPA, Meeting, 1973 November (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NASEPA, Meeting, 1974 January (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NASEPA, Meeting, 1974 September (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NASEPA, Meeting, 1974 October (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - NASEPA, Meeting, 1975 June (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Central Atlantic Environment Center, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - National Governor's Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1975 January (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, 1975 January (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, 1975 February (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1975 February (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, 1975 March (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1975 March (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, 1975 April (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1975 April (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, 1975 April (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, 1975 May (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, 1975 May (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, 1975 June (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, Executive Director, 1975 June (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator, 1975 June (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, Executive Director, 1975 July (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator, 1975 July (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator, 1975 August (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, Executive Director, 1975 August (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, Executive Director, 1975 September (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator, 1975 September (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Reader's file, Anne H. Cloude and Reggie Wallace, 1975 October (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, Executive Director, 1975 October (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator, 1975 October (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, Executive Director, 1975 November (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, Executive Director, 1975 November (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator, 1975 November (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Reader's file, Anne H. Cloude, 1975 November (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Energy report [Electrical generating systems and alternatives, Southside Electric Cooperative and Randolph Hydroelectric Project], Original and drafts, ca. 1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Economic Impact of Environmental Costs Incurred by Virginia Electric and Power Company and Other Electric Utilities, Prepared by Council on the Environment, Original report, 1975 August (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The Economic Impact of Environmental Costs Incurred by Virginia Electric and Power Company and Other Electric Utilities, Prepared by Council on the Environment, First draft, 1975 July (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - The Economic Impact of Environmental Costs Incurred by Virginia Electric and Power Company and Other Electric Utilities, Prepared by Council on the Environment, Distribution list, 1975 August (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The Economic Impact of Environmental Costs Incurred by Virginia Electric and Power Company [VEPCO] and Other Electric Utilities, Prepared by Council on the Environment, VEPCO response to report and Council on the Environment reply, 1975 August-September (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The Economic Impact of Environmental Costs Incurred by Virginia Electric and Power Company [VEPCO] and Other Electric Utilities, Prepared by Council on the Environment, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The Inflationary Impact of Federal Pollution Abatement Legislation report, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Report on the Impact of Environmental Controls on Electricity Costs, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary Report on the Impact of Environmental Controls on Electricity Costs, Working copies, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Preliminary Report on the Impact of Environmental Controls on Electricity Costs, Sources, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Preliminary Report on the Impact of Environmental Controls on Electricity Costs, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Preliminary Report on the Impact of Environmental Controls on Electricity Costs, Tables, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Preliminary Report on the Impact of Environmental Controls on Electricity Costs, Draft, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Preliminary Report on the Impact of Environmental Controls on Electricity Costs, Rough draft, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Preliminary Report on the Impact of Environmental Controls on Electricity Costs, Final charts, figures, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Electricity Costs Commission, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Electricity Costs Commission, Minutes, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - VEPCO, General, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - VEPCO, Annual reports, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - VEPCO, Prohibition order, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - VEPCO, Coal conversion, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - VEPCO, Pollution bonding, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - VEPCO, Thermal pollution, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - VEPCO, Monthly reports of cost and quality of fuels for electric plants, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fuel, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Allegheny Power Service Corporation, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - APCO, Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - PEPCO (Potomac Electric Power Co.), 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - DELMARVA Power and Light Co., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Old Dominion Power Co., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - MITRE Corp., undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - UWAG, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Municipal electric costs, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Co-Ops, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Air pollution, Air Board, Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Attorney General's Office, Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Water Control Board, Water pollution and permits, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
  - EPA, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - CEQ (Council on Environmental Quality), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Environmentalists, Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Strip mining, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Thermal pollution, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Library notes, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Policy options, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, General, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Costs, Statistics, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous file, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Presentation to Council, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Off-Shore Ports Task Force, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1975 January-February (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1974 March-May (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1975 June-August (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1975 September-October (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1975 November-December (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Congratulations, 1971-1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Citizen's suggestions, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Acknowledgments of materials sent, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, Maurice B. Rowe, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Southern Interstate Nuclear Board, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Wilderness Society, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Conservation Council of Virginia, Inc., Meeting, 1973 October (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Conservation Council of Virginia, Inc., Meeting, 1974 May (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Conservation Council of Virginia, Inc., Meeting, 1974 July (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Reader's file, Gerald P. McCarthy, Executive Director, 1975 December (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - Reader's file, Susan T. Wilburn, Environmental Impact Statement Coordinator, 1975 December (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Reader's file, Anne H. Cloude, 1975 December (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Land Use Committee, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Solid Waste and Recycling Committee, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - Solid Waste and Recycling Committee, Meeting, 1975 November (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Water Law and Policy Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  - Water Resources Committee, Meeting, 1975 December (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, Executive Committee, 1974 November (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1974 December (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, Executive Committee, 1975 March (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1975 March (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, Executive Committee, 1975 May (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1975 June (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1975 September (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, Executive Committee with Governor Godwin, 1975 October (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1975 November (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1973 March (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1973 July (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1973 December (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1974 March (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1974 June (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1974 September (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, Executive Committee, 1974 October (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Council on the Environment Meeting, 1974 October (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1974 April (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1974 June (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1974 August (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources ("10 Problems"), 1974 September 6 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1974 September 16 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1974 November (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1975 January (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1975 March (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1975 May (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1975 July (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1975 August (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Meeting with Earl J. Shiflet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1975 December (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Conservation Council of Virginia, Inc., Meeting, 1975 November (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement [PEIS] correspondence with local environmental agencies, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Federal Highway Administration [FHWA], Interagency Environmental Coordination Workshop, 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Interns, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - General correspondence, Requests for information or publications, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
  - Ohio EPA publications, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Junior League, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Xerox Community Involvement Program, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
  - Virginia State Fair, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - United Givers Fun Campaign, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Training seminars for tv appearances, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Employment Commission Public Employment Program, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Procedures manual mailing list, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Impact Statement procedures manual mailing list, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Impact Statement procedures manual, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Public hearing, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Ground quarry problems, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - VEPCO financial statement, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Energy Facilities Siting Act, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Army Logistics Management Courses, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Workshops, seminars, etc., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - VCU class, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Commission conference, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Mid-Atlantic Federal Regional Council Region III, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Conservation tour, 1974 September (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Northeast Regional Forum conference, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Phone calls and visitors, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Problems, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Temple, T. Edward, 1974-1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Energy use and power plant siting, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Sweet Briar Symposium on Energy, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Energy Center Site Survey, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Solar Energy Conference, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Study of Long Range Water Supply Problems, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Water Control Board procedures, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Potomac Water Resources Regional Compact, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Federal Water Control, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Water Control Board Hampton Roads Sanitation District, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Water Control Board, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Water Control Board, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Water Control Board, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Water Control Board, 1974 April-July (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Water Control Board, 1974 July-1975 January (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Water Control Board, 1975 February-July (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Water Control Board, 1975 August-December (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Joint Center for Urban Environmental Studies, 1974-1975 (Folder 5)
  - Solid Waste Disposal, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Virginia's Conservation Council, 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Virginia's Conservation Council, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Virginia's Conservation Council, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Virginia's Conservation Council, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Farm Bureau Association meeting, 1973 November (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - VEPCO, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Environmental education, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Environmental education, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture Forest Service, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Soil Conservation Service, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Council on Environmental Quality, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - EPA, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - EPA lead poisoning, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - IPA (Intergovernmental Personnel Act), 1972 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Air Pollution Control Board, Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Air Pollution Control Board, Correspondence 1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Air Pollution Control Board, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Air Pollution Control Board, Complaints, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Noise pollution, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Noise pollution, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Articles: Air pollution, 1970-1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Articles: Agriculture and Commerce - Articles of Interest 1970-1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Articles: Assateague Island - Coal, 1970-1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Articles: Coastal Zone - Education, 1970-1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Articles: Electricity costs - Emission, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Articles: Energy, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Articles: Environmental Goals Task Force - Environmental Matters in General, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Articles: Environmental Protection Agency - Game and Fish, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Articles: Gas - Gathright Dam, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Articles: Governor Godwin - Green Spring, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Articles: Hampton Roads Energy Company, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Articles: Highways and Transportation - Industry, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Articles: I-66 - James River Basin Study, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Articles: Kepone, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
  - Articles: Land Use - Marine Resources Commission, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Articles: Marriott Corp. - Nuclear Power, 1970-1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Articles: Offshore Ports - Oil, 1970-1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Articles: Open burning - Outer Continental Shelf, 1970-1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Articles: Parks - Power Plant Siting, 1970-1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Articles: Recycling - Scenic Rivers, 1970-1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Articles: Sewage - Southeast Va. water shortage, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Articles: State Corporation Commission - Swift Creek Mill Reservoir, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Articles: Urban housing - Wastes, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Articles: Water Board, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Articles: Water pollution - Wetlands, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
  - Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, Division of Forestry, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Address forms, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Attorney General, 1972-1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Meeting regarding data banking, 1975 June (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - EPA Resource Conservation and Recovery Act, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Conservation Council of Virginia, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Marriott Corp. Project, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Division of State planning and Community Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Capital expansion project, Opposition, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Downtown expressway, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - A Study to update and expand the Tidewater Area Central Hospital Laundry Feasibility Study, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Assoc. of American Railroads vs. EPA, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Dept. Conservation and Economic Development, Mined land reclamation, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - State Board of Health, Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Publications, "Environment", 1971 April (Vol. 13 No. 3) - 1974 September (Vol. 16 No. 7) (Box 39)
  - Publications, "102 Monitor", 1974 January (Vol. 3 No. 12) - 1976 July (Vol. 6 No. 6) (Box 39)
- Series IV: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 29900], 1974-1977., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (20 boxes). (Box 1-20)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 1, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 3, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 4, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 4, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 5, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 6, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 6, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 7, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 7, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 8, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
  - Environmental report, Construction Permit Stage, Douglas Point Nuclear Generating Station, Units 1 & 2, Volume 9, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Notices, 1977 January-November (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Notices, 1977 January-November (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Notices, 1976 March-June (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers), Baltimore District Applications, 1976 March-1977 February (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Huntington District Applications, 1976 May-November (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - ACOE (Dept. of the Army, Corps of Engineers) Section 401, Norfolk Applications, 1976 July-September (Box 8, Folder 3)